usage: deep [-h] COMMAND ...

Deep — Next-generation Distributed Version Control System

positional arguments:
  COMMAND
    init          Initialize a new empty Deep repository
    add           Add file contents to the staging index
    commit        Record changes to the repository history
    status        Show the working tree and index status
    log           Display commit history logs
    diff          Show changes between commits or the working tree
    branch        Manage repository branches
    checkout      Switch branches or restore files
    merge         Merge branches or histories
    rm            Remove files from the working tree and the index
    mv            Move or rename a file or directory
    reset         Reset HEAD to a specific state
    rebase        Reapply commits on top of another base
    inspect-tree  Internal: Inspect raw tree entries (debug)
    tag           Create or manage release tags
    stash         Stash temporary changes
    migrate       Upgrade repository to native Deep v2 format
    config        Manage repository configuration
    clone         Clone a repository into a new directory
    push          Upload local changes to a remote
    pull          Fetch and merge changes from a remote
    fetch         Download objects and references from another repository
    ls-remote     List references in a remote repository
    remote        Manage tracked remote repositories
    mirror        Create a full 1:1 mirror of a repository
    daemon        Start the Deep network daemon
    p2p           P2P discovery and direct synchronization
    sync          Smart repository synchronization
    server        Manage the Deep platform server
    repo          Manage platform-hosted repositories
    user          Manage platform user accounts
    auth          Platform authentication management
    pr            Manage platform Pull Requests
    issue         Manage platform Issues
    pipeline      Interact with CI/CD Pipelines
    web           Open the visual dashboard
    commit-graph  Manage the commit graph index
    doctor        Run repository health checks
    benchmark     Performance benchmarking suite
    graph         Visualize the commit graph
    audit         Show security and action audit logs
    verify        Verify repository object integrity
    fsck          Verify object connectivity and validity
    repack        Consolidate objects into packfiles and generate bitmaps
    sandbox       Execute commands in a secure environment
    rollback      Undo the most recent transaction
    ai            Deep AI assistant tools
    ultra         Advanced system optimization tools
    batch         Execute atomic batch VCS operations
    search        Search through repository history
    gc            Run repository garbage collection
    maintenance   Run repository maintenance tasks
    version       Show Deep version information
    debug-tree    Inspect tree contents with hidden character visibility
    help          Show this help message and exit

options:
  -h, --help      show this help message and exit

Core Commands:
  init, add, commit, status, log, diff, branch, checkout, merge, rebase, reset, rm, mv, tag, stash, migrate

Remote & Distributed:
  clone, push, pull, fetch, remote, mirror, daemon, p2p, sync

Platform & Server:
  server, repo, user, auth, pr, issue, pipeline

Diagnostics & Dev Tools:
  doctor, benchmark, graph, audit, verify, sandbox, rollback, ultra, batch, search, gc, version

Help:
  deep <command> --help
  deep help
